Why are you here?!
The spell to keep me asleep wore off.
That's not what I mean!
I know the spell wore off!
How could you just waltz up to
me after what I did to you?!
Oh, that's what you meant?
I didn't think what you did
was that horrible, really.
Do you... even have any
idea what I did to you?
I had every intention of killing you!
That's definitely not true.
I mean, if you really wanted to kill me,
it would've been way easier to just
kill me on the spot than use dark
magic to make me sleep.
I came here because I wanted another
chance to really talk to you.
Talk?
Yes.
When I looked at you then,
you were crying... and you looked like
you were in terrible pain.
So I wanted to try once more to
get you to talk to me.
Stay away!
Oh, no!
Maria-san!
The black fog is growing bigger!
What?!
Sirius, why would you do this?
Where did you get your dark magic?
Answer me, Sirius Dieke!
Sirius?
He doesn't exist anymore.
Sirius died a long time ago!
What are you saying?
Eight years ago,
someone I treasured deeply was
taken from me here.
They ruined my happiness!
Episode 12
The Final Event Has Begun...
The tea you make has such a gentle flavor.
I practiced just so I
could make you happy, Mom.
Thank you.
I'm blessed to have such a wonderful son.
The child has awakened.
Now we can begin.
My beloved little one...
Soon, you will have a new body.
Now, bring the sacrifice.
Mom!
Stop it!
Do not handle him roughly.
He is going to become my precious Sirius.
Marchioness Dieke, if you despise me,
I don't care what you do to me!
Just spare my son, please!
What impudence!
You took my husband from me and
were blessed with a child,
and you still demand more?!
I only kept the marquis company that one
time because he ordered me to on a whim!
I have no intention of
going anywhere near him again.
I only want to live a quiet life with my child!
I will not...
I will not allow only the two
of you to live a happy life!
Now, it's time to begin.
Begin what?
My son is afflicted with an incurable disease.
The poor thing doesn't have much time left.
But with dark magic, I can control one's mind
and transfer memories from one to another.
All my son needs is a healthy body,
and he can live.
Fulfill this need for my son!
If you'll do that, I'll forgive you!
Oub grisa
Ioralle
Yiavonn
Eltenfor
Federid
Yidegrahde
Itendor
Wilgwolle.
Mom!
Please... avenge me.
Well? Did it work?
Yes, milady.
We have succeeded in acquiring
dark magic, as the texts stated.
Good. Now...
Transfer Sirius's memories into
this boy's body.
You are all I have.
I can depend on no one else.
So I won't let you die, my Sirius!
It is done.
Mo...ther...
Sirius! It's you!
The dark magic was successful!
Milady, my work here is done.
May I return to my family
now, as you promised?
Yes, of course. I'll return you
to them immediately.
Why... did you deceive me?!
To let you live would be too great a risk.
Curse you!
I won't let you get away with this!
I swear I'll see you rot in hell!
Finish him.
Sirius's memories told me
that my playboy father, the marquis,
had an affair with my mother, who was a maid.
That woman loathed my mother for it,
so she sacrificed her in
order to acquire dark magic.
If all had gone according to
that woman's plan,
I would no longer be myself,
but only the vessel
that would become Sirius Dieke.
But her plan failed.
That woman just wanted to
continue clinging to Sirius
so that she could feel better.
The memories transferred to
me were only information.
They weren't Sirius's actual
thoughts or feelings.
Also, for some reason, I acquired dark magic.
I figured I could use it to get my revenge.
I've been playing the good boy all
this time, pretending to be Sirius...
so that I can inherit the Dieke family name
and destroy everything that woman holds dear!
That's what happened?
And that's why you're in such pain...
You hypocrite!
Do you think you can save me
like you did all those others,
Good Saint Catarina Claes-sama?!
If this goes any further, we're all in danger!
Catarina!
Sister!
I'll be fine.
I know I can't save you.
I'm not the heroine here, after all.
I'm just the villainess,
here to play the heroine's rival.
Of course I can't save anyone.
I can't save you from your suffering.
but I can stay by your side.
Just like they all did for me,
I can stay by your side, hear you
out when you're sad or hurt,
and not leave you until you're feeling better.
What's wrong?
Sitting out here crying won't
make it stop hurting.
I'll stay here with you.
I won't leave you until you're feeling better.
So don't cry all alone,
Raphael.
How do you know my...
Raphael...
Please... live.
Live... and be happy.
I love you.
What are you doing?
Don't listen to what this woman says!
If you take them all hostage,
you can still get out of this!
No!
I'm done trying to get revenge!
What?!
I remember everything now!
My mom's last words...
She wasn't telling me to avenge her!
Just who are you?!
So you've figured it out.
You're the man who killed my mother!
You found your way inside my mind,
and you've been controlling me all this time!
I was only helping you fulfill your own wish.
It's true that I hate them...
And I hate that woman.
But I didn't survive just so
I could get revenge!
I survived so I could find happiness!
I won't allow you to be happy!
Traitor!
It's okay.
I'm done living for revenge!
I don't need you!
The black fog is dissipating...
Sirius Dieke...
His real name is Raphael Walt.
He said that he would tell the
authorities everything
and left the school.
I want to make my mother's wish come true.
I'm going to atone for my sins and start over.
President...
His testimony exposed the crimes of
Marchioness Dieke and her underlings.
I miss having the student council
president around,
but I've avoided the bad ending in
which everyone gets killed.
Still... I can't let my guard down just yet!
The game's final event,
the second-years' graduation party,
is still to come!
There, it's all done.
I let out the midsection a bit,
but you should be careful not to overeat.
I know! Thanks, Anne!
The time has finally come.
Whether I meet my doom or not
depends on today's graduation party!
Our 19,800th strategy meeting
will now commence.
The day of the second-years'
graduation party is finally here!
The game's heroine, Maria, leaves
in the middle of the party
to confess her love to
the object of her affections!
m 0 0 l 37.5 0 l 37.5 7.5 l 0 7.5
Maria
Please allow me to stay by
your side from now on.
Please allow me to stay by your side from now on.
Whether Maria has a
happy ending or a bad ending
will determine the course of
Catarina's future!
To be exiled, or to be killed by
the conquerable characters...
We've made all the preparations we
could to avoid both.
Yes.
She's been preparing for
this ever since she was little.
Let's go over things one last time!
Right!
The toy snake she carries to
scare Geordo is in her pocket!
All the things she'll need to
survive in exile are packed.
So everything is ready.
All we can do now is hope for the best!
This meeting is now adjourned!
It's the culmination of the past eight years.
Bring it on if you must, doom flag!
I, Catarina, will take you on!
Take care, Catarina-sama.
Congratulations on your graduation,
Nicol-sama!
Thank you.
Brother.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Nicol-sama, this is for you.
Oh, thank you.
I have a present for you, too!
Here you go. I hope you like it.
Catarina-sama, what is that?
What's going on?
What's up with this grass?
How rude! That's not just grass!
I call it a veggie bouquet!
A veggie... bouquet?
I figured it would be boring to
get nothing but flowers,
so I made a bouquet out
of vegetables from my farm!
Instead of just a decoration to
throw away later,
I thought you'd like something that
would fill your belly!
Thank you. I'll eat it with gratitude.
Maria hasn't made her move yet.
The two of them have already started
performing together...
No sign of Keith or Nicol leaving
with Maria, either.
I don't think the game even had a scene
where Geordo and Alan performed together...
What's going on?
Did this somehow turn into the
reverse harem route,
where Maria ends up with all of them?!
I never cleared the reverse harem route,
but Acchan told me that Catarina is
doomed at the end of it, too!
What are you going to do, Maria?!
Are you going for a reverse harem,
or are you going to end up with one of them?!
The party will be over soon!
Why aren't you doing anything, Maria?!
Sister, I think you're eating too much.
Huh? Am I?
I've been a little worried about something.
I didn't even realize I was eating so much.
I think your stomach is what you
should be worried about.
Catarina-sama, please have my
cake, as well, if you'd like.
And mine!
Thanks.
I'm just going to go get a drink.
My fate depends on the direction
Maria's love life takes!
I can't wait around any longer!
Hey, Maria!
Is there someone you like?
I'm very fond of you, Catarina-sama.
Um, Maria...
I'm happy to hear that...
but that's not what I mean.
Is there a boy that you like and
want to have a relationship with?
A boy I like and want a relationship with...
Come on, tell me straight-up!
Maria, who are you going to end up with?!
No, there isn't.
Huh?
There aren't any boys I'm interested in.
The only one I love, admire,
and want to be with for all time
is you, Catarina-sama.
So please allow me to stay by
your side from now on.
Th-That's the line she says to the
guy she conquers in the game!
Why is she saying it to me?!
I won't allow you to get
ahead of me, Maria-san.
I'm staying with Catarina-sama forever, too!
Me, too!
Catarina-sama, please allow me
to be with you forever and ever!
Then I'd like to be with you, too,
for as long as I may.
Th-Then so would I!
What are you all talking about?
Catarina is engaged to me.
Geordo-sama, as I've told you many times,
my sister isn't fit to
serve as a prince's consort.
Keith, as I've told you many, many times,
I will absolutely never break
off our engagement.
Perhaps it's time for you
to outgrow your big sister.
Could this be...
It is! It's the friendship ending!
The heroine doesn't end up with anyone,
but the story ends with everyone
being good friends.
It might be considered a bad
ending by romance game standards,
but this means I'm not doomed!
I did it! I avoided my doom ending!
Thank you all so much for coming today.
Brother, please come visit us
at school whenever you like.
You'll fall behind the others if you don't.
Everyone, we have dessert, too.
Please help yourselves.
Wow! It looks even tastier than usual today!
Did you make it?
Yes, my mother and I
came up with a new recipe.
Your mother?
She thought you might get tired of
eating the same sweets all the time,
so she helped me come up with a new recipe.
I see!
Be sure to thank her for me, too.
I will.
We have tea, as well, Catarina-sama.
Thanks, Mary!
Let's eat!
This is...
President!
I'm not the student council president anymore,
but thank you for inviting me.
We invited him because we knew it'd
make you happy, Catarina-sama.
And we kept quiet so it would be a surprise.
I had no idea!
I'm so happy to see you, President!
Uh, I mean... Raphael-sama!
Are you coming back to school?
No, I'm sad that I wasn't able to graduate,
but I'm going to be working for
the Department of Magic now...
as Raphael Walt.
I see!
I guess that means we'll be
able to see you again.
I guess so, since it's here on campus.
In spite of everything that happened,
would you allow me
to stay by your side, Catarina Claes-sama?
Of course!
And you don't have to use that title with me.
Just call me what you've always called me.
Right in front of her fiancé...
You've seduced yet another one, Sister.
Seriously, that girl...
Now I have yet another rival.
That's our Catarina-sama.
Come, everyone, let's eat.
Spring is here.
Yes, it certainly is, darling.
When I was reincarnated as a villainess in an
otome game where all routes led to my doom,
I spent my days complaining about how
my luck couldn't be any worse.
But now,
I can say loudly and proudly...
that I, Catarina Claes, am truly blessed
to have met all these wonderful people.
I have no idea what's
going to happen from now on.
A new season that wasn't in the game's
script is about to begin!
HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
By the way, as for that one thing
I never got a chance to use...
It looks real!
Wow, it's so cool!
Dad, I want that!
It's now available to purchase,
and it's a big hit in town!